# Gustavo Toledo

São Paulo 🏦

+55 (11) 9 8688-2668 📞

gusttaa00@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/gustaf-toledo in

https://cutt.ly/9kxRVhI (#)

Young enthusiast who has grown up in the IoT era. Proficiency in Fullstack Development using JavaScript, TypeScript, Node, Angular, Nest and Knex. Database creation, modeling and analysis with SQL. Always researching paths to develop profit using modern and future Technologies.

#### **Skills**

- JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript
- Node, Nest.js, Knex, Express
- Angular, React, etc.

- SQL (PGSQL, MSSQL, MySQL, SQLite...)
- Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github...
- Agile and Design Thinking (Scrum)

## **Experience**

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

## **Programmer Analyst Intern / Grupo Memorial**

Maintenance and assistance of the ERP using Java/JSF; Using Angular, Nest.js and Knex to migrate the ERP; Trello integration for ticket opening using Automate.io; Developed the listing part of our intern framework, using Angular and Nest.js; Developed a full SDK for lugu (Financial Module) integration and a lot more.

AUGUST 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

### **Volunteer Web Developer / Centro Paula Souza**

Leader and responsible for developing and deploying Fatec Guarulhos Web Site; Using React and Bootstrap for a SPA; Applied concepts of mobile first and clean-code; Deployment using Netlify.

#### **Formation**

FEBRUARY 2020 - DECEMBER 2022

#### Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas / Fatec

Elected as Class Representant and has one of the highest grades between all Fatec's with a 9.15 PR.

#### **Certifications**

English Proficiency is Fluent; German Proficiency is Basic; Bokmål, Nynorsk Proficiency is Basic Technical Certificate Degree in Montagem e Recuperação de Computadores by Instituto Dom Bosco

Certificate Degree in Agile Meets Design Thinking by Coursera - University of <u>Virginia</u>
Certificate Degree in Introduction to IoT by Cisco Networking Academy